Guide to the Divinity School Records, circa 1920-2005 UA.19.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files, circa 1920-2005; 156 Linear Feet; 109 boxes
  - Accession A90-78
    - Divinity School - Dean's Club, 1980-1983 (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment, 1979-1982 (Box 42)
    - Faculty and Administrative Committees, 1981-1984 (Box 42)
    - Financial Aid Matters, 1972-1981 (Box 42)
    - Graduate Executive Meetings, 1982-1985 (Box 42)
    - Graduate Program in Religion, 1980-1984 (Box 42)
    - Self-Study (Cushman), 1970 (Box 42)
    - Benjamin N. Duke Fellows Program, 1978 (Box 42)
    - York Chapel Redfurbishing, 1981-1982 (Box 42)
  - Accession A93-129
    - Census Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 42)
    - Faculty Executive Council, 1973-1979 (Box 42)
    - Faculty Retreat, 1976 (Box 42)
    - Thomas A. Langford - Conversations with Faculty, 1976 (Box 42)
    - Annual Retreat, Berchtesgaden, Germany, 1972-1973 (Box 42)
    - Communion Meditation, October 3, 1971, 1971/1982 (Box 42)
    - Director of Field Education, 1963-1973 (Box 42)
    - Christian Ministerial Education - Opening Convocation, 1971 (Box 42)
    - Field Education Internships, 1968-1969 (Box 42)
    - Summer Recreational Interns, Durham, NC, 1968 (Box 42)
    - Summer Field Education, 1970-1972 (Box 42)
    - Duke Student Field Work Association, 1971-1973 (Box 42)
    - Meeting with Student Pastors - Raleigh, NC, 1974 (Box 42)
    - Faculty Executive Council - Business, 1969-1970 (Box 42)
    - Faculty Living Accomodations and Benefits, 1957-1965 (Box 42)
    - Accomodations - Visiting Faculty, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Associate Dean for Curricular Affairs, 1974-1979 (2 Folders) (Box 42)
    - Faculty Biographical Data Dossier - Form, 1960-1965 (Box 42)
    - Faculty Summer Addresses, 1968-1969 (Box 42)
    - Faculty Elections - Official Ballots, undated (Box 42)
    - Faculty Lecturer, 1965-1967 (Box 42)
    - On-the-Job Inquiries - Workmen's Comp., 1960 (Box 42)
    - Faculty Retreat, 1967 (Box 42)
    - Faculty Grant, 1967 (Box 42)
    - Faculty Sabbatical Opportunity, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Policy and Appointments Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 42)
    - Special Notices to the Faculty, 1968-1970 (Box 42)
    - Visiting Professorships, 1959 (Box 42)
    - General Letters to the Faculty from the Dean, 1966-1970 (Box 42)
    - Governance - Divinity School, 1971 (Box 42)
    - Memo - Dean Cushman, Curriculum, 1968 (Box 42)
    - Course Schedukes, 1976-1977 (Box 42)
    - Admissions, 1971-1975 (3 Folders) (Box 42)
    - Admissions, 1976-1977 (Box 43)
    - Admissions Committee Folder, 1975-1976 (Box 43)
    - Associate Dean for Curricular Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 43)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1970-1972 (Box 43)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1973-1974 (2 Folders) (Box 43)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1974-1975 (Box 43)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1975-1976 (2 Folders) (Box 43)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1975-1980 (Box 43)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1976-1980 (Box 43)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1980-1981 (Box 43)
    - Divinity School Faculty Retreat - Cancelled, 1980 (Box 43)
    - Academic Standing Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 43)
    - Administrative Staff, 1980-1981 (Box 43)
    - Association of Theological Schools, 1971-1981 (4 Folders) (Box 43)
    - Divinity School Full Professors, 1980 (Box 43)
    - Division Faculty Meeting, 1980 (Box 43)
    - Lecture Committee, 1981 (Box 43)
    - Divinity School Committees, 1980-1981 (Box 43)
    - Administrative Staff, 1976-1980 (Box 43)
    - Black Seminarians, 1981 (Box 43)
    - Black Church Studies Center, 1974-1979 (2 Folders) (Box 43)
    - Report of Black Church Affairs, 1980 (Box 43)
    - Evaluation of the Dean, 1982 (Box 43)
    - Robert Van Buskirk, 1979-1982 (Box 43)
    - Faculty Executive Council, 1971-1976 (Box 43)
    - Graduate Program Executive Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
    - Graduate Program Executive Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 43)
    - Graduate Studies in Religion, 1975-1976 (Box 43)
    - Graduate Studies in Religion, 1976-1977 (Box 43)
    - Field Education Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 44)
    - Financial Aid Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
    - Student Representative Assembly, 1973-1976 (Box 44)
    - Students - Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 44)
    - Student Representative Assembly - Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 44)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1971-1979 (7 Folders) (Box 44)
    - Faculty Notices, 1972-1979 (8 Folders) (Box 44)
    - Faculty Bulletin - Corrected Copy, 1962 (Box 44)
    - Divinity School Committees, 1975-1979 (Box 44)
    - Closing Convocations, 1970-1983 (Box 44)
    - Opening Convocation, 1969-1982 (4 Folders) (Box 45)
    - Commencement, 1964-1982 (12 Folders) (Box 45)
    - Commencement Programs, 1947-1970 (Box 45)
    - Dedication Addresses, 1972 (Box 45)
    - The Divinity School - Closing Convocation, 1970-1978 (Box 45)
    - Senior Commencement Invitation, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Frank S. Hickman Lecturer, 1968-1969 (Box 45)
    - James A. Gray and Frank S. Hickman Lecture Brochures, Convocation, 1950-1980 (Box 45)
    - Correspondence Re: Convocation Lectures, 1960-1981 (Box 45)
    - N.C. Pastors' School, 1971-1976 (Box 45)
    - Convocation and Pastors' School, 1961-1981, 9 folders (Box 45)
    - Convocation and Pastors' School Programs, 1949-1967 (Box 45)
    - Committee on Lectures and Public Events, 1961-1964 (Box 45)
    - Gray Lectures Misc., 1965, 1981 (Box 45)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1961-1965, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Loose Class Materials, 1969, undated (Box 45)
    - God - As a Word of Our Language, undated (Box 45)
    - Publications of Alumni Association, 1960 (Box 45)
    - Annual Conference Statistics, 1960-1965 (Box 45)
    - Alabama-West Florida Conference, 1960 (Box 45)
    - North-Alabama Conference, 1959-1966 (Box 46)
    - Arkansas Conference, 1961 (Box 46)
    - Baltimore Conference, 1959-1967 (Box 46)
    - Florida Conference, 1959-1967 (Box 46)
    - Holston Conference, 1959-1964 (Box 46)
    - Kentucky Conference, 1960-1967 (Box 46)
    - Louisiana Conference, 1960 (Box 46)
    - Louisville Conference, 1960-1966 (Box 46)
    - Memphis Conference, 1960-1966 (Box 46)
    - Mississippi Conference, 1959-1964 (Box 46)
    - General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 46)
    - Commons Room, 1967 (Box 46)
    - Constitution, 1963 (Box 46)
    - Loyalty Fund, 1959-1968 (Box 46)
    - Luncheon, 1967 (Box 46)
    - Alumni Records Office, 1959-1967 (Box 46)
    - National Council, 1966 (Box 46)
    - Executive Committee Alumni Association, 1961-1967 (Box 46)
    - Alumni Files and Mailing Lists, 1961-1967 (Box 46)
    - Newsletter, 1966-1967 (Box 46)
    - Christian Education Program, 1959-1960 (Box 46)
    - Clippings, 1957-1959 (Box 46)
    - The Urban Community - PT147, 1959 (2 Folders) (Box 46)
    - North Carolina Conference, 1960-1967 (Box 46)
    - Western North Carolina Conference, 1960-1966 (Box 46)
    - The Institute for Homiletics Studies - Western N.C. Annual Conference, 1965 (Box 46)
    - North Mississippi Conference, 1960-1964 (Box 46)
    - Ohio Affiliation, 1965 (Box 46)
    - Oklahoma Conference, 1966 (Box 46)
    - South Carolina Conference, 1960-1967 (Box 46)
    - Tennessee Conference, 1960-1964 (Box 46)
    - North Texas Conference, 1961 (Box 46)
    - Virginia Conference, 1959-1966 (Box 46)
    - West Virginia Conference, 1960-1967 (Box 46)
    - Alumni in Missionary Service, 1966 (Box 46)
    - Goodwin, James W., undated (Box 46)
    - Foreign, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Committee on Alumni Affairs, 1959-1967 (Box 46)
    - Annual Conferences, 1969 (Box 46)
    - Alumni Association, 1959-1966 (2 Folders) (Box 46)
    - Class Reunions, 1961-1968 (Box 46)
    - Annual Conference Representation, 1968 (Box 46)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1961-1968 (Box 46)
    - Divinity School Alumni Affairs, 1958-1960 (Box 46)
    - Rev. F. B. Peele, 1933 (Box 46)
    - Marshall C. Pickens, 1932-1938 (Box 46)
    - A - General, 1944-1948 (2 Folders) (Box 46)
    - B - General, 1940-1948 (2 Folders) (Box 46)
    - C - General, 1946-1948 (2 Folders) (Box 46)
    - D - General, 1948 (Box 46)
    - D - General, 1940-1947 (Box 47)
    - Dumont, R. E., 1942-1949 (Box 47)
    - E - General, 1944-1950 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - F - General, 1941-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - G - General, 1944-1948 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - H - General, 1939-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - I - General, 1947-1948 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - J - General, 1945-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - K - General, 19447-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - L - General, 1945-1948 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - M - General, 1944-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - Markham, C. B., 1943-1945 (Box 47)
    - Mc - General, 1945-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - N - General, 1945-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - O - General, 1945-1947 (Box 47)
    - P - General, 1945-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - Q - General, 1947-1948 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - R - General, 1945-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - S - General, 1946-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - Sands, Alex H., Jr., 1929-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - T - General, 1945-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - Telegrams, 1942-1949 (Box 47)
    - U - General, 1946-1947 (Box 47)
    - V - General, 1944-1948 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - W - General, 1944-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - Whedbee, Rev. J. C., 1939-1940 (Box 47)
    - Y - General, 1946-1949 (2 Folders) (Box 47)
    - Dean Cushman, Misc., 1959-1962 (Box 47)
    - McCullough, Dr. Gerald O., 1958-1963 (Box 47)
    - Spann, J. Richard, 1953-1959 (Box 47)
    - Maddox, George L., Occupational Goals 1961 (Box 47)
    - Andrews, George R., MD., 1959 (Box 47)
    - Manchester, Alan K., 1953-1957 (Box 47)
    - Miller, Haskell M., The Church and Planned Parenthood 1961-1962 (Box 47)
    - Gibson, J. Nelson, Jr., 1961 (Box 47)
    - Renovation of Divinity School Rooms 110 and 106, 1959 (Box 47)
    - Gray Lecturers, 1949-1960 (Box 47)
    - Marsh, John, 1957 (Box 48)
    - Martin, Stanley H., 1953-1957 (Box 48)
    - Jones, Edwin L., 1955-1957 (Box 48)
    - Interseminary Movement, 1953-1958 (Box 48)
    - Garber, Bishop Paul N., 1957-1958 (Box 48)
    - Knox, John (Gray Lecturer), 1954-1957 (Box 48)
    - Gross, John, 1953-1958 (Box 48)
    - Elliott, William F., 1956 (Box 48)
    - Ehlhardt, George B., 1954-1957 (Box 48)
    - Deans - Theological Seminaries, 1953-1958 (Box 48)
    - Cowell, Marvin J., 1958 (Box 48)
    - Cannon, W. R., 1954-1958 (Box 48)
    - Cannon, Dean James, 1958 (Box 48)
    - DeVyver, Frank T. - Asst. Provost, 1961-1962 (Box 48)
    - Clinic in Preaching, 1957-1958 (Box 48)
    - Christian Convocation, 1957 (Box 48)
    - The Methodist Board of Education, 1954-1958 (Box 48)
    - Engagements, 1959-1963 (2 Folders) (Box 48)
    - Alumni, 1958-1964 (Box 48)
    - Summer Session Faculty, 1958-1963 (Box 48)
    - Divinity School Readers, 1958-1963 (Box 48)
    - Scholarships, Financial Aid, and General Business, 1959-1962 (Box 48)
    - Scholarship and Financial Aid Committee Meeting Minutes, 1959-1961 (Box 48)
    - Divinity School Long Range Planning, 1959 (Box 48)
    - American Theological Library Association Development Program, 1961-1962 (Box 48)
    - North Carolina Council of Churches, 1958-1962 (Box 48)
    - Stokes, J. Lem II, 1956-1957 (Box 48)
    - Convocation, 1959 (Box 48)
    - Approved Supply Pastors' School and Convocation, 1959-1961 (Box 48)
    - Divinity School Retreat - Camp New Hope, 1960 (Box 48)
    - Institute of Family Law, 1959 (Box 48)
    - Dumont, Randolphe E., 1959-1961 (Box 48)
    - Opening Exercises, 1953-1954 (Box 48)
    - National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA, 1955-1958 (Box 48)
    - Faculty Degrees, 1952-1954 (Box 48)
    - Faculty Publications, 1953-1958 (Box 48)
    - Faculty Bulletins, Vols. 1-4, 1958-1962 (Box 48)
    - Clinic, 1967 (Box 48)
    - Final Exam, undated (Box 48)
    - Old Papers, 1966 (Box 48)
    - Old Exams and Grades, 1967 *RESTRICTED* (Box 48)
    - Recommended Books, undated (Box 48)
    - Duke Endowment Association Proposed Constitution, 1941 (Box 48)
    - Student Lists, 1942-1943 (Box 48)
    - Correspondence Re: Student Fieldwork, 1943 (Box 48)
    - Undergrad Ministerial Students - Applications and Letters of Recommendation, 1941-1944 (2 Folders) (Box 48)
    - Church Maintenance, 1943-1944 (Box 48)
    - Correspondence Re: Summer Work for Duke Endowment Divinity School Students, 1943 (Box 48)
    - Requests for Duke Endowment Students, 1943 (Box 48)
    - Student Summer Work Reports, 1943 (Box 48)
    - Student Lists Summer, 1942 (Box 48)
    - Misc. Correspondence, Minutes, and Papers, 1955-1958 (Box 48)
    - N. C. Dept. of Correction, 1970 (Box 48)
    - Student Pastors Roster, 1969-1970 (Box 48)
    - Student Pastors Applications, 1967-1970 (Box 48)
    - Summer Assistants, 1965-1967 (Box 49)
    - Summer Program, 1967-1970 (Box 49)
    - Supervision Committee, 1960 (Box 49)
    - Supervisors' Reports, 1970 (Box 49)
    - Th.M. Placement, 1969 (Box 49)
    - Winter Assistant Supervisors' Meeting, 1967 (Box 49)
    - Winter Assistants, 1965-1967 (Box 49)
    - Policy, 1969-1972 (Box 49)
    - Kale's Report, 1959-1961 (Box 49)
    - Pastors' Meetings - Supervisors Consultation, 1968-1970 (Box 49)
    - Prospects, 1970 (Box 49)
    - Reports, 1970 (Box 49)
    - Student Pastors' Orientation, 1962-1968 (Box 49)
    - University City Parish, 1970 (Box 49)
    - Urban Training - Webber, 1969 (Box 49)
    - Pastors' School House Requirements, 1967-1968 (Box 49)
    - Triangle Ministries, 1967-1968 (Box 49)
    - Taxi Driving Seminar, 1968-1969 (Box 49)
    - Ministry to Seamen, 1965-1970 (Box 49)
    - Pamlico Parish, 1970-1971 (Box 49)
    - N. C. Council of Churches, 1967-1968 (Box 49)
    - National Parks, 1969-1970 (Box 49)
    - Hinton Rural Life Center Internship, 1969-1970 (Box 49)
    - Church in Industry, 1967-1970 (Box 49)
    - Summer, 1969 (Box 49)
    - Bogue Banks Resort Ministry, 1968-1970 (Box 49)
    - Duke Endowment Student Association, 1967-1971 (Box 49)
    - North Wilkesboro District, 1966 (Box 49)
    - Salisbury District, 1965 (Box 49)
    - Statesville District, 1965 (Box 49)
    - Thomasville District, 1965 (Box 49)
    - Waynesville District, 1966-1968 (Box 49)
    - Winston-Salem District, 1965-1967 (Box 49)
    - Virginia Districts, 1967 (Box 49)
    - Georgia Districts, 1967 (Box 49)
    - South Carolina Districts, 1968-1969 (Box 49)
    - United Church of Christ, 1966-1969 (Box 49)
    - National Council of Churches (Dan Schores) 1966-1967 (Box 49)
    - Memo: Conference on The Church's Ministry in Leisure 1969 (Box 49)
    - Fieldwork Education Program, 1965-1971 (Box 49)
    - Pastors' Information Seminar, 1968-1969 (Box 49)
    - Korean Ministry, Triangle Area, 1968 (Box 49)
    - Policies, 1965-1966 (Box 49)
    - Durham District, 1965-1969 (Box 49)
    - Burlington District, 1965-1969 (Box 49)
    - Elizabeth City District, 1965-1969 (Box 49)
    - Fayetteville District, 1965-1967 (Box 49)
    - Goldsboro District, 1965 (Box 49)
    - Greenville District, 1965 (Box 49)
    - New Bern District, 1966-1969 (Box 49)
    - Raleigh District, 1965-1968 (Box 49)
    - Rocky Mount District, 1965 (Box 49)
    - Sanford District, 1965-1966 (Box 49)
    - Wilmington District, 1966-1970 (Box 49)
    - N.C. Conference Office, 1964-1970 (Box 49)
    - Western N.C. Conference Office, 1964-1969 (Box 49)
    - Albemarle District, 1965 (Box 49)
    - Charlotte District, 1965-1970 (Box 49)
    - Greensboro District, 1965 (Box 49)
    - High Point District, 1965-1966 (Box 49)
    - Study of Edgemont Community Center, 1969-1973 (2 Folders) (Box 49)
    - Edgemont Community Center Board Meeting Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 49)
    - Edgemont Community Center Staff Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 49)
    - Edegemont Community Center Financial Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 49)
    - Edgemont Community Center, 1968-1971 (2 Folders) (Box 49)
    - Religious Resources for Responding to Drug Abuse Victims, 1973 (Box 49)
    - Operation Breakthrough, 1968 (Box 49)
    - Internship News, 1970-1971 (Box 49)
    - E.C.C. - Board of Revitalization Committee, 1971-1974 (2 Folders) (Box 50)
    - Interseminary Church and Society Program, 1971-1972 (Box 50)
    - Industrial Internships, 1970-1971 (Box 50)
    - Intern Placements, 1969-1971 (Box 50)
    - Internship - American Farm School, 1969-1970 (Box 50)
    - Internships - Reports on Student Performance, 1970 (Box 50)
    - Campus Ministry Internship, 1964-1971 (Box 50)
    - Church and Society Intern Board, 1968-1969 (Box 50)
    - Church and Society Intern - Industry, 1945, 1968-1969 (Box 50)
    - Columbia Maryland Ecumenical Intern, 1967-1968 (Box 50)
    - Inner City Internship, 1964-1968 (Box 50)
    - Local Church Internship, 1968-1971 (Box 50)
    - Parish Internships, 1967-1969 (Box 50)
    - Student Pastor Internship, undated (Box 50)
    - World Mission Internship, 1968-1969 (Box 50)
    - Other Internship Proposals, 1968-1969 (Box 50)
    - Boca Raton, Florida, 1970-1971 (Box 50)
    - Student Association Commissioning Service, 1968-1970 (Box 50)
    - Duke Endowment Student Association, 1969-1970 (Box 50)
    - DESA Fall Training, 1968-1970 (Box 50)
    - DESA Camping Weekend, 1968 (Box 50)
    - June Training, 1969-1970 (Box 50)
    - Summer Orientation, 1970 (Box 50)
    - Spring Training, 1970 (Box 50)
    - Instructional Audio/Visual Aids, 1961-1967 (Box 50)
    - Duke Endowment Orientation Materials, 1967 (Box 50)
    - Ministry-in-Context Program *RESTRICTED* 1970-1972 (2 Folders) (Box 50)
    - Advance Newsletter, 1946-1948 (Box 50)
    - Board of Temerpance Materials, 1938-1939 (Box 50)
    - Joint Division of Education and Cultivation, 1941-1948 (2 Folders) (Box 50)
    - Executive Committee Minutes: Division of Home Missions and Church Extension, 1946-1948 (Box 50)
    - Executive Committee Division of Foreign Missions Minutes and Pamphlets, 1941-1948 (Box 50)
    - Photographs: Divinity School Students - J.M. Ormond Pictured, 1940-1942, undated (Box 50)
    - Photographs: Divinity School Building, Classroom, Library, Shelving, and John K. Benton, 1950, undated (Box 50)
    - Student Fieldwork Agreements, 1944 (Box 50)
    - Replies Re: Minimum Salary, 1947 (Box 50)
    - Office Expansion, 1945 (Box 50)
    - Louisville Administration, Wachovia Trust, Carolin Power and Light, 1928-1940 (Box 50)
    - Invoice Receipts, 1947 (Box 50)
    - Journal: Woman's Division of Christian Service of the Board of Missions and Church Extension, 1945-1946 (Box 50)
    - Board of Missions and Church Extension, The Methodist Church, 1944, 1948 (2 Folders) (Box 50)
    - Minutes - General Executive Committee, 1948 (Box 50)
    - Minutes of the Meeting of Committee on General Conference Legislation of the Board of Missions and Church Extension, 1947-1948 (Box 50)
    - Appendices, A-E, 1947-1948 (Box 50)
    - Board of Missions and Church Extension Exhibits A & B, undated (Box 50)
    - Report of Committee on Surplus Funds, undated (Box 50)
    - Board of Hospitals and Homes, NC Conference, undated (Box 50)
    - Board of Missions, Methodist Episcopal Church Organization Meeting Minutes, 1944 (Box 50)
    - The Durham Methodist Society, 1948 (Box 50)
    - Mrs. W.F. Craven by J.M. Ormond, undated (Box 50)
    - Annual Report: Interboard Committee on Missionary Education, 1944 (Box 50)
    - Joint Committee on Missionary Personnel Meeting Minutes, 1948 (Box 51)
    - Duke Endowment Student Funding, 1943-1950 (Box 51)
    - Requests for Duke Endowment Men, 1946 (Box 51)
    - Western N.C. Conference Caravan Schedule, 1943 (Box 51)
    - Teaching Materials, How Nations Share c.1935 (Box 51)
    - Advance Newsletter, 1944-1947, undated (2 Folders) (Box 51)
    - Student Government Association Minutes and Business, 1958-1960 (Box 51)
    - Student Bulletins, Vols. 1 and 2, 1959-1960 (Box 51)
    - Association of Methodist Theological Schools, 1952-1963 (2 Folders) (Box 51)
    - American Association of Theological Schools, 1953-1961 (2 Folders) (Box 51)
    - Divinity School Annual Report (Yale University), 1952-1954 (Box 51)
    - Kennedy, Gerald. Gray Lecture, 1956-1958 (Box 51)
    - Crusade Scholarships, 1954-1955 (Box 51)
    - Acknowledgement for Checks, 1959-1962 (Box 51)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1955-1963 (Box 51)
    - Student Government Association - Minutes and Business, 1960-1961 (Box 51)
    - Conference Dates, 1961 (Box 51)
    - South Carolina Conference, 1957-1958 (Box 51)
    - North Carolina Conference - Report of the Divinity School, 1957-1961 (Box 51)
    - American Association of Theological Schools - Papers Re: Divinity School Library, 1961 (Box 51)
    - World Consultation on Theological Education, 1961 (Box 51)
    - North Carolina Conference - Board of Ministerial Training, 1954-1961 (Box 51)
    - A Program of Capital Expansion for the Superior Education of a Protestant Ministry Adequate to the Needs of Tomorrow, 1962 (Box 51)
    - Faculty Letters Concerning Pensions, 1954-1955 (Box 51)
    - Conference on the Ministry, 1966-1967 (Box 51)
    - National Council of Churches, 1965-1967 (Box 51)
    - Secretaries - General, 1954-1964 (Box 51)
    - Secretarial Help, 1953-1958 (Box 51)
    - Secretary Positions Terminated, 1960-1963 (Box 51)
    - Student Bulletin, Vols. 2, 4, 5, 1961-1963 (Box 51)
    - Student Body Meeting Minutes, 1956-1958 (Box 51)
    - Student Council Meeting Minutes, 1961-1963 (Box 51)
    - West Virginia Conference, 1957 (Box 51)
    - Western North Carolina Conference, 1954-1963 (Box 51)
    - Statement by Dean Cushman, undated (Box 51)
    - Graduate Facutly Meeting Minutes, 1958-1962 (Box 51)
    - Southeast Jurisdictional Conference, 1952-1956 (Box 51)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Council, 1960 (Box 51)
    - Gerontology, 1959 (Box 51)
    - Undergraduate Ministerial Fellowships Correspondence (Alphabetical) 1931-1940 (Box 51)
    - Ministerial Student Lists, 1930-1940 (Box 51)
    - Letters and Applications, Undergraduate Ministerial Students, 1931-1938 (3 Folders) (Box 51)
    - Letters and Applications, Undergraduate Ministeral Students, 1931-1938 (Box 52)
    - North Carolina Conference Board of Missions and Church Extension, 1933-1941 (3 Folders) (Box 52)
    - Board of Missions Reports, 1933-1939 (Box 52)
    - A - Correspondence, 1929-1941 (3 Folders) (Box 52)
    - Anderson, Dr. Stonewall, 1927-1928 (Box 52)
    - Anderson, Dr. W.K., 1941-1943 (Box 52)
    - Alexander, W.M., 1938-1940 (Box 52)
    - B - Correspondence, 1931-1941 (2 Folders) (Box 52)
    - Badges - St. Louis Button Co., 1940-1941 (Box 52)
    - Badges - Eagle Regalia Co., 1940-1941 (Box 52)
    - Badges by Weaver Samples, 1940-1941 (Box 52)
    - Badge Samples and Solicitations, 1940-1941 (Box 52)
    - Bills, 1927-1941 (Box 52)
    - Sample Bulletins, 1927-1937 (2 Folders) (Box 52)
    - C - Correspondence, 1930-1941 (2 Folders) (Box 52)
    - Credits, 1940-1941 (Box 52)
    - D - Correspondence, 1932-1941 (Box 52)
    - Duke Institute of International Relations, 1933-1940 (Box 52)
    - E - Correspondence, 1928-1941 (Box 52)
    - F - Correspondence, 1928-1940 (Box 52)
    - Form Letters, 1927-1941 (Box 52)
    - G - Correspondence, 1928-1941 (Box 52)
    - H - Correspondence, 1928-1941 (2 Folders) (Box 52)
    - J - Correspondence, 1931-1940 (Box 53)
    - Jobs, 1941 (Box 53)
    - K - Correspondence, 1928-1941 (Box 53)
    - L - Correspondence, 1929-1940 (Box 53)
    - Mc - Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 53)
    - M - Correspondence, 1927-1941 (2 Folders) (Box 53)
    - N - Correspondence, 1928-1941 (Box 53)
    - N.C. Board of Directors Meeting, 1940-1941 (Box 53)
    - O - Correspondence, 1936-1940 (Box 53)
    - P - Correspondence, 1928-1941 (2 Folders) (Box 53)
    - Panel Discussions, 1939 (Box 53)